Ana channel, applause!
This is my guest Pekopa.
Please.
Can you please stop with the first time flirting?
I don't get it.
I'm not used to it, am I?
When I'm next to you.
I'm not used to it.
We're good friends.
It's written in the script.
Of course it's written in the script.
Don't pick at me.
What's today?
What's today, Anna?
What's today from both sides?
How would I know?
This time, in collaboration with METABIRTH TV
to create an original game for the Ana Channel program.
Thank you very much.
METABIRTH TV is a program we are running.
METABIRTH TV is a program we are running, and we are planning to make a game.
There is an app called Roblox.
There is an app called "Roblox" where people can create their own games.
And you can actually log in and play them.
Do you know it? Loblox.
Hmm?
I don't know.
It's really great.
It's amazing.
You know, for elementary school kids.
I mean, even a little kid like that.
They can make the games they want to make.
They can make it.
They can make it by themselves.
They don't have to do it, they can make it.
I can do it.
I can start from the making stage.And I can do it from the beginning of the process of making it.
People from all over the world.
They can make a game.
People from all over the world come there and play.
It's amazing.
And some of them
If you develop a game and your game becomes a hit
and make more than 1 billion yen.
Wow.
It's a dream, right?
I have a dream.
Yes, I do.
I want to do it.
I want to.
I know you do. Oh! Okay!
I want a billion.
No, no, no, no.
You said you wanted to do it.
I said I want a billion.
That's why I feel like I can make it.
It's not that easy.
I have the power to create.
You are a creator.
That's right.
This is probably more fun than Iketani's project.
I think this one is more fun than Iketani's project.
Not really.
Too much.
Too much.Not much.
Not much.
The cartoon development.
In a metabasic program.
The game we made
Let's play a game together.
I'll play it with you.
Thank you.
Let's play.
If you like it.
If you like it...
I think she'll want to make something like this.
I'm sure he'll come up with something like this.
So, first of all, let's play the game we, Pecopa, invented, "Escape from the Teresa! Let's play "Pecopa of Sadet"!
It's amazing, isn't it? The stage is set inside this TV Asahi station.
Yes, and it's covered in zombies!
Zombies?
There are zombies everywhere.
In TV Asahi?
There are zombies in Teletext, and the game is to go to the upper floors of TV Asahi and escape.
Sounds fun!
There are all kinds of zombies and mazes and stuff.
Well, let me try to explain it to you.
Yes, that's right.
So you don't actually see it?
Oh, yeah.
Oh, wow.
You can download the app now.
That's great.
Look at that.
Oh, there's Ano!
There's the icons of all of you.
Wait a minute, wait a minute, wait a minute.
Ano, she's the size of my head.
And super stylish.
Actually, I do, too, but isn't this a little too deflated? This.
I mean, it looks amazing, but...
I'm trying to manipulate this thing to get out of this TV Asahi.I'm going to manipulate this thing to get out of this TV Asahi.
You can also jump.
If you jump and climb, you can escape from zombies.
Why don't we start with these stairs?
Climb the stairs.
It's very sensitive.
There's a chance you'll go flying out the side.
Oh, I'm getting rather high.
Yes, now you're talking to me.
Oh my God, it's about to start because I'm in here.
Oh, man, I want to get out.
Oh, I can't get out.
Oh, come on, guys.
Can we all do this?
Can we all do this together?
I'll just be a minute.
Come on, come on, come on.
Here it comes... the door.
Yeah, I want to go in.
I'm in.
There's Ano.
Hey, I'm coming in.
Let's put him in here.
I'm in.
This place is awesome.
Okay, so let's get the hell out of here... from the upper floors.
So, there's some kind of LCD screen.
Yeah, look for a key.
It says, "Find the key and open the emergency door.
So we're going to find the key.
So you have to find the key, Ano.
Ano, first you look for the key, and then we'll go together.
There's some kind of door.
It won't open without the key.
If you don't open the key...
I'll open the door.
It won't open.
That's right, because there's no key.Yeah, because I don't have the keys.
Ano, find the keys.
Find the keys?
Come on, come on, come on.
Where are they?
I'm sitting in the chair.
Why don't you look for them?
I'm at my desk.
Here's the key.
That's it, isn't it?
That's it.
I'll get the keys.
Why do you have to do everything?
Why don't you let Ano do it?
Sit at the door.
You're sitting there.
Ano, you never move from in front of the door.
Where are you, Ano?
I'm on the couch.
There you are.
Here.
The boss is sitting here.
He's sitting.
He's the only one sitting there.
The president's desk.
He's at the president's desk.
Everybody's here.
Okay, I'll open it.
Did you get it?
Yeah, I'm ready to open it now.
Is that a tap?
Pick it up.
I got it.
Okay, let's go.
It's open.
Come on, come on, come on.
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
The door's closed.The door's closed.
What?
What do I do next?
There's some kind of key.
It's in the cardboard box.
Find it, Ano.
It says it's on top of the cardboard.
I'm making copies.
What are you doing?
Top of the cardboard.
What? Where is it?
I don't know.
Oh, there it is.
There it is.
Look at this cardboard box up here.
You mean this cardboard box?
There it is!
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's great.
All right, guys.
Where's the key?
Let's open the door.
What do we do now?
I'm in.
Oh, this is it.
Is this the right way?
This one's fine.
Oh, no?
Is it right?
What's next?
Next.
There's something in there! There's a zombie!
I see zombies!
Run, run, run, run.
Hey, it came out of nowhere.
Where are the zombies?
Zombie something, mute the zombies, watch out for zombies.Zombie something... watch out for zombies on mute.
Oh, I'm here, I'm here, I'm here.
What? Where are you?
I don't see any zombies.
Where are you?
Who else can see you?
Zombies are just minding their own business in that tea plantation.
Oh, no, the zombies are gone.
Oh, there's some zombies around the perimeter.
What? Where?
Where?
Oh, there they are.
Oh, there's a zombie on mute.
I don't see any, huh?
What happens when you see a zombie?
Do you run away? Do you run away?
You'll die if you get hit.
Oh, I saw the clue.
Oh, where?
In the trash.
All right, in the trash.
What's that?
What's happening to me?
I was killed by a zombie.
I was killed.
Oh, my God.
I don't know what's going on, but don't let it kill me.
That wasn't Mr. Silent Time, was it?
Who was that?
Who is that? Did you confuse Mr. Silent Time with a Silent Time zombie?
He's the wrong color.
You're back to the start.
Oh, here it comes.
This way, this way.
I found the keys.
Here, in the trash.
Here's the key.Here's the key.
Come on, come on, come on, everybody. Come on.
I got it, I got it, I got it.
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
Got it?
Which way's the perimeter?
Zombie or perimeter?
I don't know.
Shupe ladies.
Oh, zombies. Shupe zombies.
Oh my God, there's zombies.
Here, here, here.
Here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here.
Here we go.
It's open.
All right.
Here we go.
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
Here, you can pick up the gun. Pick up the gun.
Oh, yeah, a gun.
You can attack with a gun?
Gun.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
How do you do that?
What?
How do you shoot this thing?
The target's bigger, so it's easier to hit.
It's a big head.
Wait a minute.
Did you just shoot her?
What?
What? I heard something weird.
Ehhhh!
Oh, no!
Run! You!
Nooooo! It's huge!
Help! Help, guys! No!Help! Help me, guys! Oh, no!
Isn't this scary?
Run, run, run!
My watch has gone back.
You're fast. You're a zombie.
Oh, no, we're running out of time!
Oh, no, no, no, no! Zombies everywhere!
Oh no, oh no, oh no!
Shoinji got us. Let's go back in time.
Run, run, run, run!
Oh no, zombies on the perimeter.
Okay, run.
Yeah! Yes! Yes! Yeah!
Yeah!
Scary!
That's a good one, I'll give you that.
If I shoot this thing, can I beat it? What's this?
Can you beat this?
If I shoot this, can I beat it? I don't think so.
I think we can take it down.
Can you get it over? It's not gonna budge at all.
Aah! Hey!
It's the hacksaw!
How hard can it be?
It's pretty hard.
Oh, my God! You're in here?
That was out of the blue.
That's not fair. It's awesome that you're in.
You're a real pain in the ass, aren't you?
Careful, I'll be there when you get in.
Okay, 30 seconds left.
Oh, no.
How do I beat this?
Aah! Biccup!
Okay, I got it.
You don't have to.
Where are you going?
The goal.Goal.
Here?
Aah!
Hey, why are you here? Why are you here? Why are you here?
Why are you here?
Oh, shit! Oh, shit! Oh, no!
I'm here! I'm coming!
No! No! No! No! No! No!
You're not gonna make it! Go!
So, what if they don't kill us?
Not yet! What?
He's down. He's down for the count.
They're waiting for us.
Oh, no!
Oh, no! Oh, no! That's hard!
Let's spar and the three of us can go in together.
Yeah! Let's do it!
Let's all three of us go in together.
Let's all work together.
Let's just get out of here. Somebody dies, and you two run away.
What? I'm back.
What? When?
What? I'm in the wrong place.
What's that?
Where?
I just barely made it in time.
You made it?
Well, it's me and Anna.
All right, let's go in.
I don't have a gun.
I'll take him down.
Go, Ana, go.
Here she comes!
There you go. Go through that doorway, Anna.
Straight, straight, straight.
Here they come!
Oh, no, you got me!
Oh, no, I'm hit!Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes!
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
I think I'm gonna run away, don't you?
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
I don't care, just go ahead!
I'm good, I'm good, I'm good, I'm good, I'm good!
Yeah! I'm out!
I'm good, just go ahead!
I don't care, just go ahead, guys!
All right, all right.
I'm gonna stay upstairs...
Oh, here she is, Anna!
Here I am.
Oh! What?
This guy?
Right here. Right up there.
Did you two make this?
We came up with the idea and programmed it.
Ugh, it's dead again. I don't think I'm gonna make it.
I'm dead.
I see. You can't fall. Down.
Zombies.
How do we get down here?
I don't know.
It's so hard to get down here.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Let's focus.
You're playing a normal game.
I'm just playing a normal game.
Okay, here we go!
It's okay, but...
Oh, no, no, no, no, no!
The controls are a bit...
It's a little difficult.
Oh, I fell.
I did it!
Yes! Yes, I did it!
Yes! Keep going!All right! Keep going!
Go!
Yeah!
What? This way?
It's already over here.
This one?
Yeah, just fly over there.
Yeah!
Whew.
Shupe, you want to stop?
Shupe, I'll wait for you.
So, I thought it would be fun if the three of us said "Se-no" together.
[fast forward]
Fast forward.
[fast forward] [fast forward]
There's a zombie! Oh, no!
Oh, no, no, no, there's zombies!
Dobira, can I come in?
Zombies!
Oh, no!
A zombie! A zombie child!
We're not gonna make it.
There's a zombie farmboy!
He's right up against the wall.
Oh, my God!
I thought he was a zombie!
Oh? Oh?
Oh! I saw a light!
There's a zombie!
No! Up there!
Zombie, we're closing the door.
Oh! There she is!
I'm going too fast.
Which way did he go?Which way did he go?
That way.
Right.
That way?
Right, right.
Is this the right way?
Here, here.
Here?
What? How do I get up here?
This way? Straight up?
Whoa! There's zombies all around!
There it is! There's light! There it is! Yeah!
There it is, there it is, there it is! Oh, no!
Zombie Pompi! There's so many zombies!
What? Oh, there's another room upstairs!
Is it still there, sixth floor?
Wow! There's so many!
There's so many zombies!
Oh, my God! Oh, my God! Oh, no!
Wait a minute, does this mean we have to ride?
What?
I blew my face off.
Wait a minute. What's going on? There's so many of them.
Aro's here, too.
Oh, my God.
I'm scared.
Oh, no, no, no, no, there's so many of them.
What are we going to do?
They're chasing us!
Like this? This is impossible!
You have to go over the top.
You have to jump somewhere.
Oh, you mean like that?
Wait a minute. There's too much of it.
Like this?
It's going up.
How many floors are there?
This is the last one.This is the last one.
What?
I've already reached the finish line.
Yashiro! I'm sorry, Masai.
Yasiro, I'll wait for you. Masai, so...
Masai, can you climb this ladder? Yashiro, I don't think so, some...
Masai, come here, Yasiro. So, we're going sideways...
Oh, idiot! Masai, ah!
Masai, I just got killed by a Shoinchi zombie you lured here.
Yo, what?
Yo, why are you coming up here?
Masai, what? You're climbing up now? Yow, zombies are bad. They learned to climb.
Yo, zombies are growing up.
Yo, do they jump up there? After the ladder at the end. Masai, yes.
Yeah, they jump, Masai. They don't jump.
You go like this, climb up...
Hey, why are you climbing up?
You're pissing me off!
If they're climbing up, are they in a big hurry?
If we don't sit still for a minute, they might catch up with us.
Mud was climbing up so fast, so we might as well just go for it.
Yamato, it's not the pattern, it's not the pattern, it's not the pattern, it's not the pattern, it's not the pattern.
It got deeper and deeper, one by one, one by one, one by one, another white rocker, yes, yes, yes
but jump down from there already, jump down the other way, the other way, the other way, the other way, run, run, run, run!
To the left, to the left, to the left!
left, left, left, left, left!
Goal! Oh, look out!
Yay, I made it! I made it!
I'm giving up, let's go, Ano!
I'm ready... let's go, Ano...
Yay, yay, yay!
Now, the president of the Takasu Clinic is probably on board.
Nakahira and Ano-chan made it to the finish line! Ano-chan did it!
This was pretty challenging, but wow, that's great!
I'm so glad you could do it!
I'm glad. I'm glad. I'm glad we're done for today.
Even we came up with the idea ourselves!And that's how I came up with the idea myself, that we even came up with the idea ourselves.
And that's how we came up with the idea for this game.
Now that you have a better understanding of Loblox, I'll tell you what we're going to do now.
I'd like to introduce you to the creator of the game, Mr. Kamagaya, who will be working with us to create the game.
Mr. Kamagaya, the creator of the game, who will be working with us on this project, is connected to us remotely, so let's have a meeting.
Let's have a meeting.
Please do. Thank you very much.
So, Ano, what kind of games do you want to make?
You're always making pictures and clay figures on that channel.
I want you to make a character with teeth.
Mr. Kamagaya, have you ever had a tooth character?
I've learned. It's new.
Ano likes teeth, Kamagaya-san.
A game with teeth?
Yes. I wonder what it's like exactly.
Something about the game setting itself...
In the mouth.
In the mouth. In the mouth, you mean.
I see. Dungeon.
You can move it around like a dungeon.
That one player...
That one player... or that enemy...
Mr. Kamagaya, how much do you understand so far?
I'm catching up.
Catching up?
If you put your idea to Mr. Kamagaya...
I asked him if he could do it or not.
I'd like to take out the bacteria.Bikins are the enemy.
And the hero?
The hero is the teeth.
He moves inside the mouth with his teeth.
It's a little pinkish because it's in the mouth.
You know, like gums and tongue.
What do you think?
What do you think? Mr. Kamagaya.
I think it's really good.
Really?Really?
What does it do?
You know, like a jar of germs or something.
And then you brush your teeth with it.
Take it down.
How's that sound?
What do you think? Mr. Kamagaya.
What do you think?
You mean you beat the germs by brushing your teeth?
Yeah, and picking up the toothpaste on the way.
It's good for your education, right?
Yes, it is.
What do you hope to end up with when you're killing them?
Ceramic?
That's gonna take a while.
It'll be clean.
When it's clean, it's the goal.
I guess that's okay.
Yeah, it's a little sweet at first.
So it's like a tooth-brushing action game?
You know, like cleaning up a mouth full of germs.
What do you think? Mr. Kamagaya.
I think it's a lot of fun.
This is the player.
Mr. Kamagaya, can you see it now? This one.
I see it.Is that it? Is that the little Deaf Girl?
That's the little deer.
I moved the Wooly Dummies.
You want to get a few characters out of him.
If you don't beat the chicken, he'll turn into a fat cow.
So we're pretty much running out of time?
I'll set a time limit.
How's it going?
Can I ask you something?
The game takes place in your mouth.
So it's like the main character is on top of your teeth?
The other teeth are different.Other teeth are not.
Faceless teeth.
Is that background?
Because I want a tooth on top.
Okay, I see.
Are you sure? Mr. Kamagaya.
Mr. Kamagaya, you wanted to ask me if I want to do it on top of the teeth?
While moving them around in your mouth.
For example, where is the camera?
And the main character...
Can he only move sideways now?
Isn't that it? Like the one I just did, he can move around like 360 degrees,
And maybe he should be able to walk around on the tongue? Maybe.
Like going to brush your teeth.
He can move around freely.
Is that a big mouth?
It's kind of a mouth, but not really the size of a mouth,
It's like my heart is in my mouth. It's like the dressing room is in your mouth.
It's big. It's a big world, maybe. Overall.
Mr. Kumagai, let's erase the concept of the inside of the mouth.
It seems to be big anyway.
I mean, the design is in the mouth.
I see. Try to write it down.
You could put in a lot of things.
But it's too big? Anyway.
Yes, it is.
I'll ask you to draw a picture.
[fast forward].
Wait a minute, Mr. Bear.
He's writing it for me.
Like this.
What's it look like?
[Laughter]
[Staff] Mr. Kumai, it looks like this.
Pink. Just pink.
I want to express the weird bumpiness and luster of the gums and stuff like that.
Teeth? Teeth? Teeth?
There are teeth in those places.That's where the teeth are.
Yes. And they have teeth like fossils or something.
I see. So the teeth don't have to be lined up like a row of teeth?
Like a wall, like this on the wall.
Yes. How is that?
How do you like it? What do you think? Kumai-san.
I have a rough idea of what I want to do.
Amazing.
As expected.
Kumai-san is amazing.
Mr. Kumai is amazing.
I could visualize it.
That's great.
So, now that you have an image of Mr. Kumai, what would you like Ano-chan to do?
What do you want to do with what's falling down?
I'm sure it's on the floor. Toothpaste?
If you take out the toothpaste, it will be easier to remove germs and stains.
I see.
And then, on the way, you've got all kinds of dirt coming in at mealtime.
That's good.
You can have a rice ball or something.
Eat it.
Eat it, eat it, like chocolate.
Or cake.
Do you want some isodine time?
No! Coffee time.
Coffee time. It's dirty.
Coloring?
The more difficult it is, the more it is.
Ano, what's the worst thing you can put in your mouth?
What's the worst thing you can put in your mouth?
Grapefruit.
I hate grapefruit.
I love grapefruit, but it's sour and it dries up my mouth. I don't know. You know?
It dries you out?
It's like...
That's why I don't like it.
I hate it.I don't like it.
How's it going?
What do you think? Are you talking to Mr. Kumagai?
Mr. Kumagai, what do you think?
Please answer me, Mr. Kumagai.
I'm sorry.
If you have any questions, I'm totally fine.
I'd like to be more specific about what the enemy looks like.
The image of the enemy.
Do you want to draw a chicken as the enemy?
Do you want me to draw a bikin?
A new character?
Purple or Baikin?
I'll draw a purple one.
Black.
Do you want me to draw a Bikin?
Or the chicken itself?
Why not? The chicken's a chicken.
I'll make it a chicken.
Here, and here.
I'm going to call these two "Bikin.
Me too.
I'm a chicken, too.
Make Pecopao a chicken.
Can I make him an enemy? Enemy, please.
I'm going to scrub them with a toothbrush anyway.
If you add some horns or something to it, it'll look more like a bikin.
It's like an enemy.
Any ideas for a title?
What? A game title for the two of us.
Like "We're the Dead" or something like that.
What's that?
I'm cool with that kind of English.
Really?
What? Toothbrush?
Mouthwash.
Mouthwash?Mouthwash?
Tease, tease.
But maybe you should put your name in there.
Ano-chan.
I think a title like "Anochan" would be good.
Anochan...
Dental...
Anochan Dental Clinic.
Eijaku!
It's a good idea.
What do you think? Kumagai-san.
Anochan Dental Clinic.
No problem.
It's just right.
Why don't you put a subtitle on it too?
Anochan Dental Clinic, I don't know if we can manage to win.
Pecopar, Pecopar...
Kick them out.
Get rid of him.
Get rid of Pecopar!
We're starting to look like the Murali Assassins. Are you okay?
It was her idea.
Here's the base.
The bass should be like this.
Okay.
How's it going?
How about you?
How about you? I don't know.
Mr. Dreskikabake, do you think you can do it?
I think so.
Oh, wow!
I did it! I'm so happy!
Then, I'll ask you to do this for me.
I'm so happy.
Well, there is one thing I would like to ask you.
Yes, I do.
I would love to have a character drawn by Anochan appear in the game.I would love to have a character drawn by Anochan in the game.
May I ask you to design that?
Comment] I wanted to have a character drawn by Ano-chan appear in the game.
[Comment] I was wondering if Ano-chan would do it this way. No, you can do whichever you like. I'm Baikin.
[Comment] Ano-chan says she's a bikin. Ano-chan is a bikin, too.
Is it me?
[Comment] Ano, you're a chicken, aren't you? Ano, you're a bikin.
Comment] Does the concept of "game over" mean time is up? Yes, time is up.
So you can either clean it up in time, or you can't clean it up in time? Yes.
So, I think we can make it work.
I think it's totally fine even if it's arranged a little bit in your own way. I understand.
So, Mr. Kumagai will actually develop this game.
When it's ready, please have Ano come to our METABUS TV show. We will play together. I want to do it!
I'm glad you're going to be there. I want to do it!
It depends on your skill, Kumagai-san. Really.
Do me a favor at the end. It really cost a billion yen.
Oh my God! He really meant it! Mr. Kumagai's on my back!
Ano Channel] This is Ano, everyone who watches Ano Channel.
I have an announcement.
Ano Channel's distribution event will be held on August 11 at the Teresa Summer Festival.
Bye bye!
It looks like we can meet at METABUS Roppongi, so let's make summer memories together with the two guys from Pecopa!
Best regards!
Subscribe to your channel!
undefined